vacationclubap.com 2013-03-16

# Marriott Vacation Club Asia Pacific - Privacy

Introduction

Marriott Vacation Club International (“MVCI”) has a strong commitment to providing excellent service to all of our customers and members, including respecting their concerns about privacy. We understand that visitors to this website may have questions about whether and how this website collects and uses information. We have prepared this statement (“Statement”) to inform you of the privacy principles that govern this website. 

This Statement contains numerous general and technical details about the steps we take to respect your privacy concerns. We have organized the Statement by major processes and areas so that you can quickly link to the information of most interest to you. Please note that a separate privacy statement and separate terms and conditions apply to the [Marriott Rewards program](http://marriott.com/privacy.mi). 

At MVCI, meeting your needs and expectations form the foundation of everything we do – including protecting your privacy.

Marriott Vacation Club Asia Pacific is making every attempt to ensure that all our business practices that involve the use of your information are compliant with privacy regulations in Singapore. 

Marriott Vacation Club Asia Pacific may change the Privacy Policy from time to time. Each use of The Marriott Vacation Club Asia Pacific website will publish the most current version of the Privacy Policy informing you of any changes. 

If you have not agreed to the Terms of Use, you may not use, access or submit information to Marriott Vacation Club Asia Pacific website.

If after reviewing this Statement, should you have any questions or privacy concerns please send an email to [privacy@vacationclub.com](mailto:privacy@vacationclub.com) or send a letter to: 

Marriott Vacation Club Asia Pacific  
Attn: Information Protection  
6649 Westwood Blvd, Suite 500  
Orlando, FL 32821 

Browsing  
Information We Collect and Its Uses  
Create an Account Profile  
Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information  
Confidentiality of Social Security Numbers  
Disclosure of Information to Third Parties  
Children’s Privacy  
Cookies  
E-Network  
Sweepstakes  
Other Sites  
Website Survey  
Legal Issues  
Vacationclub.com Internet Privacy Statement Changes  

Return to top

Browsing

This website does not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse this website and request pages from our servers. This means that, unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us with personally identifiable information, we will not know your name, your email address, or any other personally identifiable information. When you request a page from our website, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header including the Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time of the request, the URL of your request, and other information that is provided in the HTTP header. We collect the HTTP request header information in order to make our website function correctly and provide the functionality that you see on this website. We also use this information to better understand how visitors use our website and how we can better tune it, its contents and functionality to meet your needs. 

Return to top

Information We Collect and Its Uses

When we need to collect personally identifiable information from you to execute the requested transaction or provide you with a particular service, we will ask you to voluntarily supply us with the information. For example, if you would like to make a reservation at one of our resorts, we will ask for information such as your name, address, telephone number and email address to process your reservation. We will use your email address to send a confirmation and, if necessary, might use the other information to contact you for help in processing. On occasion, we use third parties to provide or confirm for us contact information about you given the information you provided to us directly. We would then use this information for market analysis and marketing purposes. 

In addition, when you provide contact details for transaction requests such as scheduling an appointment or requesting a proposal, we will use the contact information to keep you updated about future offers or promotions unless you opt-out online or otherwise notify us. 

Return to top

Creating an Account Profile

Owners of MVCI properties or timeshare interests may, at their choice, create a personal account profile online within our password-protected Members Clubhouse. Creating an account profile makes it more convenient for by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter personal contact or preference information. In addition, if you choose, you can perform certain functions within your account. The security of this information is addressed in the security section below. You can access and review, update or deactivate the information in your account profile information online. 

We treat the information you provide to us as confidential; it is, accordingly, subject to our company’s security procedures and corporate policies regarding protection and use of confidential information. Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, additional measures that vary depending on the applicable legal requirements may be put in place. Information is generally processed and stored in Singapore and the United States. 

Please note that Marriott Vacation Club International will never send you email requesting your user name, password, credit card number or social security number. If you receive an email that looks like it’s from Marriott Vacation Club International, but asks you for your credit card number or social security number, it is a fraudulent email, or “phish.” We recommend that you do the following: 

  * Forward the email to the Federal Trade Commission at spam@uce.gov or call 1-877-FTC-HELP (1-877-382-4357) to report it. The FTC uses the spam stored in this database to pursue law enforcement actions against people who send deceptive email. 
  * Delete the email.

If you believe “phishers” have gotten access to your personal or financial information, we recommend that you also do the following: 

  * Change your password.
  * Contact credit reporting services and have a fraud alert attached to your credit report file. Please be aware that the perpetrator may attempt to use your information to establish accounts or obtain credit at other businesses in their name. 

[Learn more](http://www.marriottvacationclub.com/common/cms/mvc-main/images/legal/Additional_Information_on_Fraudulent_Emails.pdf) about fraudulent email or “phish” and how to protect your personal information. 

Return to top

Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information

We treat the information you provide to us as confidential; it is, accordingly, subject to our company’s security procedures and policies regarding protection and use of confidential information. When we ask you for credit card data, it is transferred over a Secured Sockets Layer (SSL) line, provided you are using a SSL-enabled browser such as Microsoft Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox. We also use SSL on other select pages where you would enter personally identifiable information. This ensures that your information is encrypted as it travels over the Internet. This secure mode is enabled before any such information is transmitted from your computer. You will know you are in secure mode when the padlock or key icon in the lower right-hand or left-hand corner of the computer screen appears in the locked position. In addition, when accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from “http” to “https.” 

After information reaches MVCI, it is stored on a secure server that resides behind firewalls designed to block unauthorized access from outside of MVCI. Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, our vacation resorts or other business operations may put in place additional measures that change depending on the applicable legal requirements. Information collected on this site and covered by this privacy statement is generally processed and stored in Singapore and/or the United States. 

Return to top

Confidentiality of Social Security Numbers

Social Security Numbers are restricted, confidential information and legally protected data under Federal and State laws. Social Security Numbers have been collected and retained to comply with various Federal and State laws. Marriott Vacation Club International uses employee identification numbers and customer numbers that are not derived from a Social Security Number for its general information systems. Marriott Vacation Club International uses policies, procedures, training, technology and auditing to protect the confidentiality and privacy of Social Security Numbers and to ensure that proper controls are in place concerning the collection, use and disclosure of Social Security Numbers. 

Return to top

Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

MVCI prohibits the sale or transfer of personal information to entities outside of the Marriott Vacation Club International family of companies for their use without your approval and providing the opportunity to opt-out. MVCI may share your personally identifiable information with affiliated companies that are directly or indirectly controlled by, or under common control, with Marriott Vacation Club International, Inc. MVCI may send personally identifiable information about you to non-affiliated companies that are not directly or indirectly controlled by, or under common control of, Marriott Vacation Club International, Inc. when we have your consent to share the information; need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested or we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of MVCI (e.g., mailhouses) to provide a product or service to you. These companies do not have any right to use the information we provide to them for any purpose beyond what is necessary to assist us. 

Return to top

Children’s Privacy

This site is not intended for children and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children.

Return to top

Cookies

This website uses “cookie” technology. “Cookies” are encrypted strings of text that a website stores on a user’s computer. This website requires the use of a cookie to keep information you enter together across multiple pages. This is an MVCI “session” cookie that expires when you close your browser. We also use “persistent” cookies to measure usage of various pages on our website and to help us make our information more pertinent and easy for you to access. These persistent cookies are MVCI cookies and will remain on your computer unless deleted by you. We do not use cookies to ascertain any personally identifiable information about you apart from what you voluntarily provide us in your dealings with MVCI. We also use persistent cookies as part of the functionality that allows you to request to speak with a representative while you are on the website. 

You may set your browser to block cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so may adversely affect your ability to perform certain transactions, use particular functionality and access certain content on our website. 

Return to top

E-Network

We would be delighted to have you join the Marriott Vacation Club E-Network. If you choose to join the E-Network, you’ll receive news about our resort specials and our e-newsletter, which we hope will inspire and help you plan exciting dream vacations. If you join the E-Network and later decide you no longer wish to receive these communications, you can opt-out be following the instructions in our email communications or by sending an email to [optout@vacationclub.com](mailto:optout@vacationclub.com). Please be sure to send the e-mail from the address you wish to have deleted or if sending from a different email address, be sure to include the e-mail address you want us to delete. 

Return to top

Sweepstakes

On occasion, we conduct sweepstakes that entitle the winners to prizes. Each sweepstakes has it own terms and conditions. As part of entering a sweepstakes certain personally identifiable information such as name and email address will generally be required. We may use this information to send future communications about specials and offers. 

Return to top

Other Sites

This website contains links to select third party sites that may be of interest to you (e.g., airlines, car rental companies). MVCI is only responsible for the privacy statement and content of this website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the use of cookies on websites that you have accessed this website from and to the non-MVCI websites that you may access from this website. 

Return to top

Website Survey

MVCI values your input. If you choose, we welcome your participation in an online survey regarding the usefulness of this website. The information you provide will be used only by MVCI for research and analysis and is not personally identifiable to you. 

Return to top

Legal Issues

This is a United States website and is subject to United States law. MVCI will disclose personal information without your permission when required by law, or in good faith based upon the belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful activities to MVCI members, visitors, associates, or property (including this site), or to others. Laws related to personal identifiable information vary by country. 

Return to top

VacationclubAP.com Internet Privacy Statement Changes

In the future, we may need to change the privacy statement for vacationclubap.com. All changes will be made here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. This statement was last updated on November 20, 2011. 

Return to top
